Guide to the C-SPAN records, 1809, 1978-2012
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Series 7: Education and Marketing (Boxes 145-229), 1989-2009
  - C-SPAN in the Classroom Short Subject Lesson Plans Volume 1-3, 1989-1992 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Development Grants A-P, 1990-1994 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Development Grants A-P, 1990-1994 (Box 156, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Development Grants A-P, 1990-1994 (Box 156, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Development Grants R-Z, 1990-1994 (Box 156, Folder 5)
  - C-SPAN in the Classroom 17th Seminar for Professors, August 8-9, 1994 (Box 156, Folder 6)
  - Marketing and Education Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 156, Folder 7)
  - Marketing and Education Correspondence and News Clippings, 1993-1997 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Alexis de Tocqueville Series Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 157, Folder 2)
  - Education and Marketing Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 157, Folder 3)
  - American Presidents: A Lecture Series Lesson Plans, 1995 (Box 157, Folder 4)
  - Educator's Hotline Scripts, 1997 (Box 157, Folder 5)
  - Educator's Hotline Weekly Report, 1992-1993 (Box 157, Folder 6)
  - Educator's Hotline Weekly Reports, 1995 (Box 157, Folder 7)
  - Educator's Hotline Weekly Report, 1996-1997 (Box 157, Folder 8)
  - Alexis de Tocqueville Series Correspondence, 1997 (Box 157, Folder 9)
  - Minority College Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 157, Folder 10)
  - Minority College Report, 1995 (Box 157, Folder 11)
  - Minority College Report, 1990-1991 (Box 157, Folder 12)
  - Minority College Report College Department Contacts, 1990s (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Marketing and Education Correspondence Success Stories, 1993 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Monthly Online Access of C-SPAN in the Classroom, 1997 (Box 158, Folder 3)
  - Ohio Presidents Series, 1995 (Box 158, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Development Grants, 1995 (Box 158, Folder 5)
  - Alexis de Tocqueville Series Correspondence, 1997 (Box 158, Folder 6)
  - C-SPAN in the Classroom Membership Reports-Part 1, 1991-1994 (Box 158, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN in the Classroom Membership Reports-Part 2, 1991-1994 (Box 158, Folder 8)
  - C-SPAN in the Classroom Correspondence, 1997 (Box 158, Folder 9)
  - Colleges and Universities with C-SPAN Seminar Participants, 1994-1995 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Educator's Hotline Weekly Report, 1994 (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Various Education and Marketing Files, 1997 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Tocqueville Series Academic Advisory Committee, 1997 (Box 159, Folder 2)
  - Tocqueville Series in Newport, Rhode Island, May 9, 1997 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - Tocqueville Series Website, 1997 (Box 159, Folder 4)
  - Tocqueville Series Tour and Dates, 1997 (Box 159, Folder 5)
  - Tocqueville Series Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Tocqueville Series Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - Tocqueville Series Pamphlets and Brochures, 1997 (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Tocqueville Series Correspondence, Notes, 1996-1998 (Box 159, Folder 9)
  - Tocqueville Series Tour Book, 1997 (Box 159, Folder 10)
  - Tocqueville Series Viewer Contest, 1997-1998 (Box 159, Folder 11)
  - Tocqueville Series Video Compilations, April 1997 (Box 159, Folder 12)
  - Tocqueville Series Press Releases, April 1997 (Box 159, Folder 13)
  - Tocqueville Series Programming Suggestions, 1996-1997 (Box 159, Folder 14)
  - Tocqueville Series Educational Materials, 1996 (Box 159, Folder 15)
  - Tocqueville Series General Comments and Queries, 1996-1997 (Box 159, Folder 16)
  - Tocqueville Series Goal Statement and Strategies, 1996 (Box 159, Folder 17)
  - Tocqueville Series Tocqueville Institution, 1996 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Tocqueville Series Educator's Guide, 1996 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Tocqueville Series Logo Planning, September 18, 1996 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Tocqueville Series Correspondence, 1996 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Tocqueville Series Notes and Memos, 1996 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - Tocqueville Series Colleges and Universities Along Route, 1996-1997 (Box 160, Folder 6)
  - Tocqueville Series Tour Stops, circa 1996 (Box 160, Folder 7)
  - Tocqueville Series Core Group Meetings, 1996 (Box 160, Folder 8)
  - Tocqueville Series Project Timeline, September-October 1996 (Box 160, Folder 9)
  - Tocqueville Series C-SPAN Staff Introduction Sessions, June 1996 (Box 160, Folder 10)
  - Tocqueville Series Correspondence and Notes, 1996 (Box 160, Folder 11)
  - Tocqueville Series Yale Library, 1996-1997 (Box 160, Folder 12)
  - Tocqueville Series Correspondence and Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 160, Folder 13)
  - Tocqueville Series Launch in France, April 26, 1997 (Box 160, Folder 14)
  - Tocqueville Series Tour Book, 1997 (Box 160, Folder 15)
  - Tocqueville Series Corporate Group Meetings, 1996-1997 (Box 160, Folder 16)
  - Tocqueville Series Sheila Le Suer, 1997 (Box 160, Folder 17)
  - Tocqueville Series Historical Markers, 1997-1998 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Tocqueville Series Tocqueville Bust, 1997-1998 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Tocqueville Series Cable Systems, circa 1997 (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - Tocqueville Series Fall Bus Stops with Tim Lynch Portraying Tocqueville, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Tocqueville Series Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 161, Folder 5)
  - Tocqueville Series Correspondence and Documents, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 6)
  - Tocqueville Series Correspondence, 1997 (Box 161, Folder 7)
  - Tocqueville Series Advanced Workshop for Professors, April-August 1996 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Tocqueville Series in New York City, New York, April-June 1997 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Tocqueville Series Press Clippings, May 1997-January 1998 (Box 162, Folder 3)
  - Tocqueville Series Press Clippings, May 1997-January 1998 (Box 162, Folder 4)
  - Tocqueville Series Press Clippings, May 1997-January 1998 (Box 162, Folder 5)
  - Tocqueville Series Contemporary Tocqueville References, 1995-1996 (Box 162, Folder 6)
  - Tocqueville Series Contemporary Tocqueville References, 1995-1996 (Box 162, Folder 7)
  - Tocqueville Series Marketing Materials, 1997 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Tocqueville Series Educators' Resource, 1997 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Tocqueville Series Educators Materials, 1997 (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Survey of Cable Operator Executives on Basic Network Performance: C-SPAN, 1991-1992 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation of Cable TV Services-Summary of Key Results for C-SPAN, 1989-1992 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Evaluation of Cable TV Services Amory a National Sample of Cable TV Subscribers, 1991-1992 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - Perceived Value and Satisfaction of Cable TV Services/Attitudes Toward Tiering, December 1990 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Survey of C-SPAN Audience, 1987-1988 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN Awareness/Viewing Study, 1991-1992 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN Election Study and Attitudes and Usage of Cable Television, 1992 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN National Awareness/Viewing Study, January 1991 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Viewer Recontact Survey, May 1993 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Seminar Professors Fax Broadcast Survey, February 10, 1994 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Seminar Professors Fax Broadcast Survey, February 10, 1994 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Seminar Professors Fax Broadcast Survey, February 10, 1994 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Cable Audit Associates, January 29, 1991 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN Digest Survey, August 13, 1992 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN National Election Study, November 1992 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Beta Research Corporation National Cable Subscriber Study, Fall 1992 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Beta Research Corporation National Cable Subscriber Study, Fall 1989 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Beta Research Corporation National Cable Subscriber Study, Fall 1990 (Box 165, Folder 7)
  - Education Grants, 1988-1989 (Box 165, Folder 8)
  - Education Grants, 1988-1989 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Cable Insights Seminar, February 25-26, 1993 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Cable Insights Seminar, February 25-26, 1993 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Equipment Grant Program 1991-1992, School Visit Surveys (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Equipment Grant Program 1991-1992, Press Clippings (Box 166, Folder 5)
  - Equipment Grant Program 1991-1992, Judging (Box 166, Folder 6)
  - Equipment Grant Program 1991-1992, Video Equipment Grant Application (Box 166, Folder 7)
  - Equipment Grant Program 1991-1992, Press Releases (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - Equipment Grant Program 1991-1992, Correspondence and Memos (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Equipment Grant Program 1991-1992, Zenith, Tandy, and Circuit City Information (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Education and Marketing Services Monthly Reports, February-June 1994 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Education and Marketing Services Monthly Reports, July-September 1994 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Education and Marketing Services Monthly Reports, October-December 1994 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - C-SPAN in the Classroom Seminar for Professors, Winter 1991 (Box 167, Folder 5)
  - Public Affairs Video Archive Coupon Distribution, 1991-1992 (Box 167, Folder 6)
  - Public Affairs Video Archive Coupon Distribution, 1991-1992 (Box 167, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN in the Classroom Video Equioment Grant Letters to Principles of Winning Schools, March-April 1992 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - National Equipment Grants Award Travel, 1992 (Box 168, Folder 9)
  - Education Grant Traveler Press Releases, May 1992 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - Equipment Grant Program Press, July-August 1991 (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - Marketing Affiliate and Non-Affiliate Lists and Letters to Congressmen, March-April 1992 (Box 168, Folder 12)
  - Thank-you Letters From Schools, April-June 1992 (Box 168, Folder 13)
  - Panasonic Equipment for Education Grant Winners, 1991-1992 (Box 168, Folder 14)
  - Equipment Grant Project Correspondence, April-June 1992 (Box 168, Folder 15)
  - C-SPAN Management Development Program, January 1990 (Box 168, Folder 16)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Alton Debate, October 1994 (Box 168, Folder 17)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Marketing Goals, February-March 1994 (Box 168, Folder 18)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series College-Level Resource Guide Evaluations, September 1994 (Box 168, Folder 19)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Galesburg and Quincy Debates, circa 1994 (Box 168, Folder 20)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Ottawa, Illinois, Debate, June 1994 (Box 168, Folder 21)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Press Kit and Springfield, Illinois, Dinner, March 1994 (Box 168, Folder 22)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Profiles of Debate Sites, circa 1994 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Plans and Handouts, February-May 1994 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Opportunities for Educators, April 1994 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Opportunities for Operators, February-April 1994 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Planning Meetings and Information, December 1993-March 1994 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Promotions and Premiums, March 1994 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Press Strategy and News Clippings, February-March 1994 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Staff Training, March 1994 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Marketing Action Plan, March-June 1994 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Related Organizations and Clubs, February-May 1994 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Bibliography, February 1994 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series John Splaine Correspondence, August 1993-March 1994 (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Freeport Debate Press Clip Router, August 27, 1994 (Box 169, Folder 13)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Correspondence, Evaluations, and Newsclippings, July-December 1994 (Box 169, Folder 14)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Planning and Marketing, 1994 (Box 169, Folder 15)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Newsclippings, March-August 1994 (Box 169, Folder 16)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Correspondence, April-December 1994 (Box 169, Folder 17)
  - Executive, Department Heads, Directors, Managers, and Supervisors, January 2001 (Box 169, Folder 18)
  - Community Relations Budget, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Battle Creek, Michigan, February 2001 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - American Writers Beacon Awards Entry, 2001 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Book Tour Indianapolis, Indiana, Borders and Time Warner Cable, October 2001 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - American Writers Series Thomas Paine Show in New Rochelle, New York, March-April 2001 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Community Relations Initiatives, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - American Writers Series Community Relations Strategy, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Driver, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Sharan Daniel Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Accounts Responsibilities and Guidelines, 2001 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Strategy and Tactics, 2001-2002 (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Strategies for Los Angeles Targeted Week, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - Los Angeles Media, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 13)
  - Los Angeles VIP and Influentials, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles Cable Channel Information, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 15)
  - Transmission and Technical Information, 1998-1999 (Box 170, Folder 16)
  - Cable Carriage Information, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 17)
  - Community Relations Account Assignments, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 18)
  - Community and Affiliate Relations, 1999-2000 (Box 170, Folder 19)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Visit to Dallas, Ft. Worth, and Austin, Texas, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 20)
  - C-SPAN School Bus in South Carolina, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 21)
  - C-SPAN School Bus in San Diego, California, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 22)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Weekly Reports with Grades, October-November, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 23)
  - C-SPAN Bus Upgrade, October 2000 (Box 170, Folder 24)
  - C-SPAN School Bus in Seattle, Washington, June 2000 (Box 170, Folder 25)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Meeting Notes, circa 2000 (Box 170, Folder 26)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Schedule, 2002 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles Viewer Mail, January 2002 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN Networks Carriage Summary, 2002 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - American Presidents Series Newsclippings, 1999 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - American Presidents Series Viewer Mail, 1999 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - American Presidents Series Viewer Mail, 1999 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - American Presidents Series Viewer Mail, 1999 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series Videotape Catalog, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - Lincoln-Douglas Series, A Companion, 2001 (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - Chas Fagan Illustrations and Contract, 2001 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - American Writers Book Marks, Photographs, and Magnets, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - American Writers Press Kits, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - William F. Buckley Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Betty Friedan Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - David Halberstam Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Jack Kerouac Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Ernie Pyle Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Will Rogers Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - John Steinbeck Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - Edith Wharton Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - Ernest Hemingway Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 12)
  - Langston Hughes Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 13)
  - Russell Kirk Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 14)
  - Walter Lippman Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 15)
  - H.L. Mencken Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 16)
  - Neil Sheehan Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 17)
  - Upton Sinclair Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 18)
  - Jame Baldwin Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 172, Folder 19)
  - Whitaker Chambers Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Mary Chesnut Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Black Elk Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - William Falkner Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - F. Scott Fitzgerald Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Zora Neale Hurston Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Henry Adams Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - William Bradford Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Willa Cather Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - William Clark Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 10)
  - James Fenimore Cooper Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 11)
  - Theodore Dreiser Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 12)
  - W.E.B. DuBois Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 13)
  - Ralph Waldo Emerson Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 14)
  - Nathaniel Hawthorne Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 15)
  - Thomas Jefferson Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 16)
  - Meriweather Lewis Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 17)
  - Abraham Lincoln Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 18)
  - James Madison Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 19)
  - Thomas Paine Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 173, Folder 20)
  - Theodore Roosevelt Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth Cady Stanton Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Harriet Beecher Stowe Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Henry David Thoreau Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Sojourner Truth Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Booker T. Washington Portrait, circa 2002 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - C-SPAN3 Launch Authorization Forms, 2002 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN Networks Carriage Summary, 2002 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Goals for Online Programming, 2002 (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Community Relations Correspondence, 2002 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - C-SPAN Bus Video and Presentations, 2002 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - C-SPAN Bus Scripts and Information, 2002 (Box 174, Folder 12)
  - C-SPAN Bus Schedule, 2001 (Box 174, Folder 13)
  - Peter Waso and Roger Withers Bus Driver Information, 1994-1997 (Box 174, Folder 14)
  - Employee Inclement Weather Policy, January 10, 1996 (Box 174, Folder 15)
  - C-SPAN Bus Newsclippings, 1996 (Box 174, Folder 16)
  - C-SPAN Quiz, 1992-1993 (Box 174, Folder 17)
  - C-SPAN Bus Logs, 1999-2001 (Box 174, Folder 18)
  - C-SPAN Bus #1 Redesign, 2000 (Box 174, Folder 19)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Press Kit, 1993 (Box 174, Folder 20)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Correspondence and Press Releases, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Tour Schedules and Maps, 1997 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN School Bus Correspondence and Planning, 1993 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Guidelines for Evaluating, Counseling, and Disciplining Employees, March 27, 2001 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - C-SPAN Community Relations University, August 21-25, 2000 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - C-SPAN Week, April 24-28, 2000 (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - C-SPAN Focus Group Report, June 28-July 7, 1989 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - C-SPAN Recontact Study, April-May 1993 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - C-SPAN Pricing Study, Spring 1995 (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Affiliate Relations Responsibilities-Part 1, June 1997 (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - Affiliate Relations Responsibilities-Part 2, June 1997 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - National Audience Study, Fall 2000 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - C-SPAN in the Classroom $100,000 Equipment Grant Program, 1991-1992 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN in the Classroom $100,000 Equipment Grant Program, 1991-1992 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - Campaign 2000 Educator's Conference, February 14-15, 2000 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Brumidb Project Plan, March 18, 2010 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - American Presidents Program Schedules and Correspondence-Part 1, 1999 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - American Presidents Program Schedules and Correspondence-Part 2, 1999 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - American Presidents Portraits by Chas Fagan, 1999 (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - American Presidents Programming and History Project, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - American Presidents Viewer Contest Correspondence, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - American Presidents Series Presidential Survey Newsclippings, 2000 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - American President Series Schedules and Pamphlets, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - American President Series Planning, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - American Presidents Series Correspondence and Survey, 1999-2000 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - American President Series Viewer Contest Winners, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - American President Series Viewer Contest Entries-Part 1, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - American President Series Viewer Contest Entries-Part 2, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - American President Series Viewer Contest Entries-Part 3, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 10)
  - Civil Rights Movement Series on C-SPAN Radio, 2003 (Box 177, Folder 11)
  - American Presidents Series Ronald Reagan Show Planning, 1999 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Education and Marketing Planning, 2003 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Alabama Ride to Freedom Tour, 2003 (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - American Presidents Series Herbet Hoover Show Planning, 1998-1999 (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Langston Hughes and Ernest Hemingway Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - American Presidents Series Ulysses S. Grant Show Planning, 1999 (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Jefferson Davis Show Planning, 1999 (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - American President Series William H. Harrison Show Planning, 1999 (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - American Presidents Series Zachary Taylor Show Planning, 1999 (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - American Presidents Series James Monroe Show Planning, 1999 (Box 178, Folder 10)
  - American President Series Richard Nixon Show Planning, 1999 (Box 178, Folder 11)
  - American Presidents Series Show Rundowns-Part 1, 1999 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - American Presidents Series Show Rundowns-Part 2, 1999 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - American President Series Guest Biographies, 1999 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - American President Series Shoot Arrangements, 1999 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Education and Marketing Notes and Promotional Materials, 2008-2010 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Information about C-SPAN, 1998 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Education and Marketing Outreach, 1998 (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Logosheet and 3.5" Floppy, 1998 (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - American Political Items Collectors, 2000 (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - Internet Education Websites, 2000 (Box 179, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper and Magazine Advertisements, 1997-1998 (Box 179, Folder 11)
  - Kay Erlanger Farewell Party Flyer, 1998 (Box 179, Folder 12)
  - Letter for Product Samples, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - American Presidents Pamphlets and Press Releases, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Marketing Notes, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - General Company Information, 1997 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Education and Marketing Projects, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and Information on Must-Carry Rules, 1996-1998 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Cable Carriage and Citizens for C-SPAN, 1997-1999 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - Viewer Survey, 1996-1997 (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - Viewer Services Monthly Reports, 1992-2000 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - Viewer Services Monthly Reports, 1992-2000 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - Viewer Services Premiums, 1997-1999 (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - Susan Swain Biography, June 1999 (Box 180, Folder 12)
  - Brian Lamb Biography, 1994-1999 (Box 180, Folder 13)
  - Viewer Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 180, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence and Surveys About Congressional Coverage, 1994-1996 (Box 180, Folder 15)
  - C-SPAN Audio 1 Schedules and Pamphlet, 1995 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Programming Schedule Changes, April 24, 1997 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Program Theme Music, 1997 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - C-SPAN Radio Correspondence and Schedule, 1997-1999 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Viewer Services Procedures Manual, 1999 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Quotes for About Books Promotional Kit, 1998 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Tune in Advertisement Samples and Redesign, 1998 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Registered Service Mark Usage, March 1998 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Marketing Plan, June 20, 1996 (Box 181, Folder 9)
  - Independent Contractor Agreement, 1997 (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - Facts, Goals, and Manuals, 1994-1996 (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - Digital Television, 1998 (Box 181, Folder 12)